racklodge.com 2011-11-07

# Provides Security for Personal Information

Rack Lodge takes steps to ensure it meets privacy principles and requirements with respect to personal information. The purpose of this statement is to inform our customers and other individuals we deal with how we collect, use, disclose and protect your personal information. Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, as more particularly described under applicable privacy legislation. This statement applies to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information.   
Rack Lodge will never sell, rent, lease or otherwise share any private or corporate information with anybody outside our company.

We will use commercially reasonable methods to keep Personally Identifiable Information securely in our files and systems. Our Payment System is operated using secure Internet connections, using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption, to help protect your financial data.

**Personal Information We Collect**

Rack Lodge collects personal information in a number of circumstances in the course of providing Data Center Services to customers. Personal information we collect may include: 

**Contact Information:**

  * Name, address, telephone number, email address and other contact information.

**Financial Information:**

  * Credit card numbers, bank name and billing address. 
  * Usage Information and History: Rack Lodge usernames and passwords, ip address and support ticket history.
  * Other information we may collect with consent or as permitted or required by law. 

**Use of Personal Information**

Rack Lodge generally uses personal information for the following purposes: 

  * Billing purposes, including managing, administering, collecting or otherwise enforcing accounts
  * General administrative purposes and to ensure compliance with legal, regulatory, security and processing requirements
  * Customer relations purposes; we may contact customers to ensure their satisfaction with our services.
  * Other information only by consent or as permitted or required by law.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

Rack Lodge discloses personal information only as necessary to meet legal, regulatory and security requirements, with your consent, or as permitted or required by law.   
In no event will Rack Lodge disclose any personal information about any customer to any third party without the customer's express written consent. Rack Lodge has taken security measures to ensure customer information is protected against loss, alteration or misuse. These measures include strong database encryption and secure protocols, such as SSL, when transmitting private information over the Internet.

**Service Providers**

Personal information, NOT including financial information, may also be transferred to third party agents or service providers we engage to provide technical support on our behalf. We take reasonable measures to ensure that your personal information that may be collected, used, disclosed or otherwise processed by these service providers on our behalf is protected and not used or disclosed for purposes other than as directed by Rack Lodge.

 **Security**

We protect your personal information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, which may include safeguards to protect against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Authorized employees of Rack Lodge who require access to your personal information in order to fulfill their job requirements will have access to your personal information. 

**Access, Correction and Contacting Us**

Rack Lodge may establish and maintain a file of your personal information for the purposes described above, which will be accessible at Edificio Colon Suite 2-17 San Jose Costa Rica. If you wish to request access or correction of your personal information in our custody or control, you may write to the above address, attention Customer Service. Your right to access or to correct your personal information is subject to applicable legal restrictions. If you wish to make inquiries or complaints or have other concerns about our personal information practices, you may write to us as described above, e-mail us at  [info@racklodge.com](mailto:info@racklodge.com) or call us at (506) 258-1111.

**Privacy Statement Changes**

This privacy statement may be revised from time to time. If we intend to use or disclose personal information for purposes materially different than those described in this statement, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals in advance. 

Please note that with today's current technology, we cannot fully and completely guarantee the security of your data as it travels over the Internet.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Agreement or the practices of this Site, you may contact us at **[info@racklodge.com](mailto:info@racklodge.com)**
